Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 23= (One Year Later)
=الحلقة 23= (بعد عام واحد)
Look!
ينظر!
We're finally free again!
لقد أصبحنا أحرارًا أخيرًا مرة أخرى!
Indeed.
بالفعل.
Check this out.
تحقق من هذا.
We're free again!
نحن أحرار مرة أخرى!
- That's great! - Nice!
- هذا رائع! - ​​لطيف!
Chi Yu, don't go!
تشي يو، لا تذهب!
Chi Yu!
تشي يو!
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
Summoning spells do exist, Feng!
إن تعويذات الاستدعاء موجودة بالفعل، فينج!
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪
(Don't call me Feng.)
(لا تناديني بفينج)
(My name is Chi Yu.)
(اسمي تشي يو.)
(Stop)
(قف)
(sneezing.)
(عطس.)
(When the flowers bloom,)
(عندما تتفتح الزهور)
(I'll do you a favor by watching them with you.)
(سأقدم لك خدمة كبيرة من خلال مشاهدتهم معك.)
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
The flowers have bloomed.
لقد تفتحت الزهور.
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
The flowers have bloomed.
لقد تفتحت الزهور.
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
The flowers have all bloomed...
لقد تفتحت كل الزهور...
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪
(The flowers have all bloomed.)
(لقد تفتحت كل الزهور.)
(Why aren't you back yet?)
(لماذا لم تعودي بعد؟)
(One Year Later)
(بعد عام واحد)
(Chi Yu.)
(تشي يو.)
(Chi Yu, I'm missing you.)
(تشي يو، أنا أفتقدك.)
♪The autumn wind stirs ripples on the lake♪
♪رياح الخريف تثير تموجات على البحيرة♪
♪I never saw the promised sea of blossoms♪
♪لم أرى أبدًا بحر الأزهار الموعود♪
♪Snow falls on my hair, I sing alone, your hands no longer on the strings♪
♪يتساقط الثلج على شعري، وأغني وحدي، ولم تعد يديك على الأوتار♪
(Chi Yu, is that you?)
(تشي يو، هل هذا أنت؟)
♪What we lived was never written, only carried in the heart♪
♪ما عشناه لم يُكتب أبدًا، بل حمله القلب فقط♪
♪I sigh, for all beings are bound by fate♪
♪أتنهد، لأن جميع الكائنات مرتبطة بالقدر♪
♪Helpless before a love too deep♪
♪عاجز أمام حب عميق جدًا♪
♪It leaves my body marked with scars♪
♪يترك جسدي مليئا بالندوب♪
♪Love and hate, all too brief, the years make us strangers♪
♪الحب والكراهية، كلاهما قصيران جدًا، السنوات تجعلنا غرباء♪
♪The swaying bamboo unsettles a quiet heart♪
♪الخيزران المتمايل يزعزع قلبًا هادئًا♪
♪Words by the western window hold me captive through the night♪
♪الكلمات عند النافذة الغربية تأسرني طوال الليل♪
♪It's a fleeting dream that feel all too real♪
♪إنه حلم عابر يبدو حقيقيًا للغاية♪
♪That I follow without question♪
♪أنني أتبعها دون أي سؤال♪
♪As I question the swift passing of spring, the quiet rain soaks us both♪
♪ بينما أتساءل عن مرور الربيع السريع، يغمرنا المطر الهادئ ♪
♪Time flows gently, yet I cannot bear to see it pass♪
♪يمر الوقت بهدوء، ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مروره♪
♪Sorrow etches itself into every word♪
♪الحزن ينقش نفسه في كل كلمة♪
I knew
انا عرفت
you'd be back.
سوف تعود .
(When you were severely poisoned,)
(عندما كنت مسموما بشدة)
(I inserted two golden phoenix feather)
(أدخلت ريشتين من طائر الفينيق الذهبي)
(into your body.)
(في جسدك.)
(It was supposed to be)
(كان من المفترض أن يكون)
(an eternal mark)
(علامة أبدية)
(to keep you safe for life.)
(للحفاظ على سلامتك مدى الحياة.)
(I never thought your enduring longing for me)
(لم أكن أتوقع أبدًا أن يستمر شوقك إلي)
(would awaken my golden phoenix feathers)
(سوف يوقظ ريش الفينيق الذهبي الخاص بي)
(and bring me back to life.)
(وأعيدوني إلى الحياة.)
♪It's a fleeting dream that feel all too real♪
♪إنه حلم عابر يبدو حقيقيًا للغاية♪
(Perhaps this is our Twin-soul Contract.)
(ربما هذا هو عقد توأم روحنا.)
♪As I question the swift passing of spring, the quiet rain soaks us both♪
♪ بينما أتساءل عن مرور الربيع السريع، يغمرنا المطر الهادئ ♪
♪Time flows gently, yet I cannot bear to see it pass♪
♪يمر الوقت بهدوء، ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مروره♪
♪Sorrow etches itself into every word♪
♪الحزن ينقش نفسه في كل كلمة♪
I'm back because you've missed me.
لقد عدت لأنك افتقدتني.
♪It leaves my body marked with scars♪
♪يترك جسدي مليئا بالندوب♪
♪Love and hate, all too brief, the years make us strangers♪
♪الحب والكراهية، كلاهما قصيران جدًا، السنوات تجعلنا غرباء♪
♪The swaying bamboo unsettles a quiet heart♪
♪الخيزران المتمايل يزعزع قلبًا هادئًا♪
♪Words by the western window hold me captive through the night♪
♪الكلمات عند النافذة الغربية تأسرني طوال الليل♪
♪It's a fleeting dream that feel all too real♪
♪إنه حلم عابر يبدو حقيقيًا للغاية♪
♪That I follow without question♪
♪أنني أتبعها دون أي سؤال♪
♪As I question the swift passing of spring, the quiet rain soaks us both♪
♪ بينما أتساءل عن مرور الربيع السريع، يغمرنا المطر الهادئ ♪
I will be with you
سوف أكون معك
forever.
للأبد.
♪Sorrow etches itself into every word♪
♪الحزن ينقش نفسه في كل كلمة♪
♪It's a fleeting dream that feel all too real♪
♪إنه حلم عابر يبدو حقيقيًا للغاية♪
♪That I follow without question♪
♪أنني أتبعها دون أي سؤال♪
♪As I question the swift passing of spring, the quiet rain soaks us both♪
♪ بينما أتساءل عن مرور الربيع السريع، يغمرنا المطر الهادئ ♪
♪Time flows gently, yet I cannot bear to see it pass♪
♪يمر الوقت بهدوء، ولكنني لا أستطيع أن أتحمل مروره♪
♪Sorrow etches itself into every word♪
♪الحزن ينقش نفسه في كل كلمة♪
♪Like a dream too brief, leaving only the memory of someone I once knew♪
♪مثل حلم قصير جدًا، لا يترك سوى ذكرى شخص عرفته ذات يوم♪
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 23=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 23=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪